<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Boat • logs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Boat • logs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 09:45:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Boatlogs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-boatlogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 09:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-boatlogs/</guid>
      <description>My first post welcoming readers to my personal journey through life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 id="welcome-to-boatlogs">Welcome to Boatlogs</h1>
<p>Hello and welcome to my personal blog, <strong>Boatlogs</strong>. As the slogan suggests, &ldquo;Life is Like a Boat,&rdquo; I believe that our journey through life resembles sailing across vast oceans - sometimes calm, sometimes turbulent, but always moving forward.</p>
<h2 id="why-boatlogs">Why &ldquo;Boatlogs&rdquo;?</h2>
<p>The name &ldquo;Boatlogs&rdquo; is inspired by the traditional ship&rsquo;s log that sailors keep to record their journeys, observations, and experiences at sea. Similarly, this blog will serve as my personal log of thoughts, experiences, and reflections as I navigate through life.</p>
<p>Just as a boat needs direction, purpose, and adaptability to weather various conditions, so do we in our life journeys. Through this blog, I hope to share my own experiences, challenges, and lessons learned along the way.</p>
<h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect</h2>
<p>In this space, you can expect to find:</p>
<ul>
<li>Personal stories and reflections</li>
<li>Insights and lessons from my everyday experiences</li>
<li>Thoughts on various aspects of life&rsquo;s journey</li>
<li>Photography from my travels and daily life</li>
<li>And much more&hellip;</li>
</ul>
<p>I invite you to join me on this journey, to share in the experiences, and perhaps find some resonance with your own life voyage.</p>
<p>Thank you for visiting, and I look forward to sharing this journey with you.</p>
<p><em>- Shenhai Ran</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
